St go digit star health and ICC Lombard
are in focus on the back of fresh
brokerage notes Yash is joining us with
more details on this
Yash well it's a very interesting report
which jeffre has released not just on go
digit but the entire general insurance
industry they've clearly taken sides
between the two large segments of
General Insurance sector that is motor
and health what they are saying is that
motor is expected to fire Full Throttle
whereas health is expected to remain
under some pressure for the coming time
uh what they've done on gold digit is
that they've initiated their coverage
with a buy rating Target price of 420
rupees per share uh they say that
product diversification and operating
leverage can improve the combined ratio
for gold digit to about 103% they also
expect the EPS cagr of 73% and Roe
expansion to about 16% for gold digit
General Insurance on Star health
insurance they've come out with a hold
rating Target price has been reduced to
550 rupees per share what they are
saying on Star health insurance is that
industry headin can keep profitability
under pressure also they see elevated
combined ratio of 97 to 98% over fi25 to
27 estimates with range bound Roes of 11
to 133% interestingly on ICI Lombard
they've retained the buy rating but
they've increased the Target price 2600
rupees versus 2180 rupees they expect
the combined ratio to improve by about
370 basis points 200% by F5 27 estimates
also EPS estimates have been raised
anywhere between 6 to 16% PB fintech is
another top pick for Jeff they expect
the turn turn of cycle and blanket price
hike to lead stronger growth for Pb
fintech also they say that the launch of
its claims management business can
strengthen the customer ownership and
improve the renewal ratios for pbin Tech
largely to summarize the take on the
health insurance and the motor insurance
industry uh they say that large private
insurers will gain from multi-year
upcycle in the motor insurance industry
motor upcycle will be led by
premiumization of underlying automix and
second thing moderating competitive
intensity on the health side they've
said that uh that particular segment can
see some pressure going forward and that
pressure will be led by Rising cleance
frequency and elevated competition
amongst the
players thank you very much for that uh
that's PB fintech up half a percent but
go digit is moving up get into a break
we'll come back and discuss Market
technicals mesh Tucker joins in with the
stop trading bets
[Music]